{
 "subject": "biology",
 "lesson": "l02",
 "grade": "c4",
 "quests": [
	{
		"id": 1,
		"question": "Solanum trilobatum is the binomial name ofThoothuvalai. The word ‘Solanum’ refers to",
		"options": {
			"a": "Species",
			"b": "Genus",
			"c": "Class",
			"d": "Orders"
		},
		"answer": "b"
	},
	{
		"id": 2,
		"question": "Floridian starch is a reserve food material o",
		"options": {
			"a": "Chloroplyceae",
			"b": "Phaeophyceae",
			"c": "Rhodophyceae",
			"d": "Cyanophyceae4"
		},
		"answer": "c"
	},
	{
		"id": 3,
		"question": "An example for colonial form of algae is",
		"options": {
			"a": "Oscillatoria",
			"b": "NostacOPTION 2",
			"c": "Volvox",
			"d": "Chlorella"
		},
		"answer": "c"
	},
	{
		"id": 4,
		"question": "An example for colonial form of algae is",
		"options": {
			"a": "Oscillatoria",
			"b": "Nostac",
			"c": "Volvox",
			"d": "Chlorella"
		},
		"answer": "d"
	},
	{
		"id": 5,
		"question": "One of the following is an edible mushroom",
		"options": {
			"a": "Polyporus",
			"b": "Agaricus",
			"c": "Pennicillium",
			"d": "Aspergillus"
		},
		"answer": "b"
	},
	{
		"id": 6,
		"question": "Plants that prevent soil erosion are",
		"options": {
			"a": "algae",
			"b": "fungi",
			"c": "bryophytes",
			"d": "pteridophytes"
		},
		"answer": "c"
	},
	{
		"id": 7,
		"question": "The first land plants are",
		"options": {
			"a": "bryophytes",
			"b": "pteridophytes",
			"c": "gymnosperm",
			"d": "angiosperm"
		},
		"answer": "b"
	},
	{
		"id": 8,
		"question": "The well-developed sporophytic plant body is seen in",
		"options": {
			"a": "bryophytes",
			"b": "pteridophytes",
			"c": "gymnosperms",
			"d": "angiosperms"
		},
		"answer": "c"
	},
	{
		"id": 9,
		"question": "Binominal Nomenclature was firstintroduced in the year",
		"options": {
			"a": "1970",
			"b": "1975",
			"c": "1978",
			"d": "1623"
		},
		"answer": "d"
	},
	{
		"id": 10,
		"question": "Penicillin is an antibiotic which is extracted from",
		"options": {
			"a": "algae",
			"b": "fungi",
			"c": "bryophytes",
			"d": "pteridophytes"
		},
		"answer": "b"
	},
	{
		"id": 11,
		"question": "In polypetalae, the petals are free.",
		"options": {
			"a": "True",
			"b": "False",
			"c": "",
			"d": ""
		},
		"answer": "a"
	},
	{
		"id": 12,
		"question": "Binomial name should contain more thantwo words.",
		"options": {
			"a": "True",
			"b": "False",
			"c": "",
			"d": ""
		},
		"answer": "b"
	},
	{
		"id": 13,
		"question": "Artificial system of classification is based on a few characters of the plant.",
		"options": {
			"a": "True",
			"b": "False",
			"c": "",
			"d": ""
		},
		"answer": "b"
	},
	{
		"id": 14,
		"question": "Cell wall of fungi is made up of chitin.",
		"options": {
			"a": "True",
			"b": "False",
			"c": "",
			"d": ""
		},
		"answer": "a"
	},
	{
		"id": 15,
		"question": "Pinus is a closed seeded plant.",
		"options": {
			"a": "True",
			"b": "False",
			"c": "",
			"d": ""
		},
		"answer": "b"
	},
	{
		"id": 16,
		"question": "All bryophytes are hydrophytes.",
		"options": {
			"a": "True",
			"b": "False",
			"c": "",
			"d": ""
		},
		"answer": "b"
	},
	{
		"id": 17,
		"question": "Dicotyledons have well developed characters than the gymnosperms.",
		"options": {
			"a": "True",
			"b": "False",
			"c": "",
			"d": ""
		},
		"answer": "a"
	},
	{
		"id": 18,
		"question": "Mosses are the well developed plant in bryophytes.",
		"options": {
			"a": "True",
			"b": "False",
			"c": "",
			"d": ""
		},
		"answer": "a"
	},
	{
		"id": 19,
		"question": "The dominant phase of the bryophytes is sporophyte.",
		"options": {
			"a": "True",
			"b": "False",
			"c": "",
			"d": ""
		},
		"answer": "b"
	},
{
		"id": 21,
		"question": "Cyanophyceae.",
		"options": {
			"a": "Green algae",
			"b": "Red algae	",
			"c": "Blue green algae",
			"d": "Brown algae"
		},
		"answer": "c"
	},
{
		"id": 22,
		"question": "Chlorophyceae.",
		"options": {
			"a": "Green algae",
			"b": "Red algae	",
			"c": "Blue green algae",
			"d": "Brown algae"
		},
		"answer": "a"
	
{
		"id": 23,
		"question": "Phaeophyceae",
		"options": {
			"a": "Green algae",
			"b": "Red algae	",
			"c": "Blue green algae",
			"d": "Brown algae"
		},
		"answer": "d"
	},
{
		"id": 24,
		"question": "Rhodophyceae",
		"options": {
			"a": "Green algae",
			"b": "Red algae	",
			"c": "Blue green algae",
			"d": "Brown algae"
		},
		"answer": "b"
	}
  ]
}